healthx.com 2019-04-20

# The Healthx Privacy Policy Promise

This policy was last updated on July 13, 2015. For additional details, view our terms of use.

### Does this website use cookies?

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while visiting. Cookies are small files saved to your computer that track, save and store anonymous information about your interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website to provide you with a tailored browsing experience.

By using this site, you give your consent to accept cookies.

In accordance with EU regulations, we are required to make you aware of the ways this website uses cookies.

  * This website uses cookies to personalize your experience. For example, if you have previously provided personal information on a form, we may enter that information on other forms automatically. The software that allows for this personalization uses cookies.
  * This website uses tracking software provided by Google Analytics and/or HubSpot to monitor visitor activity so that we may better understand how the site is used. The software will save cookies to your computer but will not store, save or collect any personal information.

### Which types of information do we collect?

You are free to explore our website without providing any information about yourself. However, some resources on our site require disclosure of personal information.

In this privacy policy, the term “personal information” refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us or that identifies you personally. This information may include:

  * Contact information such as your name, email address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business.
  * Information about any transactions, either free or paid, that you enter into on our website.
  * Information about you that is available on the Internet such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

The collection, use and preservation of personal information will be used only by us. We will not disclose your personal information without your explicit consent. We will never sell your personal information to any third party.

We will use the information we collect to provide the services/information requested. In addition, we may use your personal information to:

  * Send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means
  * Send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you
  * Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website, emails, and other materials
  * Provide other companies with statistical information about our users; however, this information will not be used to identify any individual user

### Will this privacy policy change?

As we evolve, this privacy policy may evolve too. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent. We will post any policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

### If the policy changes, which version applies to me?

Your continued use of our websites and/or continued provision of personal information to us will be subject to the terms of the privacy policy in place at that time.

### Does this policy apply to social media and sharing features?

Our website includes interactive mini-programs such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This privacy policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

### Does this policy apply to external websites?

Our websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This privacy policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.

### Whom do I contact with questions?

If you have any questions or concerns, contact us.
